[
    {
      "question": "______ llovía, salió a correr.",
      "answer": "Aunque",
      "options": ["Aunque", "Lograr", "Desarrollar", "Evitar"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____, terminar el proyecto.",
      "answer": "Lograr",
      "options": ["Darse cuenta", "Conseguir", "Lograr", "Mejorar"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____, nuevas ideas.",
      "answer": "Desarrollar",
      "options": ["Desarrollar", "Evitar", "Confiar", "Acostumbrarse"]
    },
    {
      "question": "El _____ paso es leer.",
      "answer": "Siguiente",
      "options": ["Siguiente", "Mejorar", "Darse cuenta", "Confiar"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Me _____ de mi error.",
      "answer": "Darse cuenta",
      "options": ["Mejorar", "Conseguir", "Lograr", "Darse cuenta"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Me estoy _____ al trabajo.",
      "answer": "Acostumbrando",
      "options": ["Acostumbrando", "Evitar", "Lograr", "Siguiente"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Debo _____ mi inglés.",
      "answer": "Mejorar",
      "options": ["Conseguir", "Lograr", "Mejorar", "Darse cuenta"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____, el error.",
      "answer": "Evitar",
      "options": ["Evitar", "Mejorar", "Siguiente", "Lograr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____, en ti.",
      "answer": "Confiar",
      "options": ["Confiar", "Lograr", "Desarrollar", "Acostumbrarse"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____, el libro.",
      "answer": "Conseguir",
      "options": ["Conseguir", "Evitar", "Lograr", "Siguiente"]
    }
  ]
  